ride_name = "Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind"

questions = [
    {
        "question": "What year did Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind open at EPCOT?",
        "answers": ["2022", "2021", "2020", "2019"],
        "correct_answer": "2022"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Disney World park is home to Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["EPCOT", "Magic Kingdom", "Hollywood Studios", "Animal Kingdom"],
        "correct_answer": "EPCOT"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the theme of Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["Guardians of the Galaxy", "Star Wars", "Avengers", "Spider-Man"],
        "correct_answer": "Guardians of the Galaxy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who designed Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["Walt Disney Imagineering", "Tony Baxter", "John Hench", "Bob Gurr"],
        "correct_answer": "Walt Disney Imagineering"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the height requirement to ride Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["42 inches", "40 inches", "44 inches", "48 inches"],
        "correct_answer": "42 inches"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the maximum speed of Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["60 mph", "55 mph", "50 mph", "45 mph"],
        "correct_answer": "60 mph"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the duration of the Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind ride?",
        "answers": ["3 minutes", "4 minutes", "5 minutes", "6 minutes"],
        "correct_answer": "4 minutes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of ride is Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["Indoor roller coaster", "Dark ride", "Simulated ride", "Boat ride"],
        "correct_answer": "Indoor roller coaster"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the ship featured in Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["Milano", "Benatar", "Star Blaster", "Dark Aster"],
        "correct_answer": "Milano"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the main antagonist in Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["Eson the Celestial", "Thanos", "Ronan the Accuser", "Ego the Living Planet"],
        "correct_answer": "Eson the Celestial"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the planet where Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind is set?",
        "answers": ["Xandar", "Earth", "Knowhere", "Sakaar"],
        "correct_answer": "Xandar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the team that the Guardians of the Galaxy belong to?",
        "answers": ["Guardians of the Galaxy", "Avengers", "X-Men", "Fantastic Four"],
        "correct_answer": "Guardians of the Galaxy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a raccoon in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "answers": ["Rocket", "Groot", "Star-Lord", "Drax"],
        "correct_answer": "Rocket"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a tree in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "answers": ["Groot", "Rocket", "Star-Lord", "Drax"],
        "correct_answer": "Groot"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is the leader of the Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "answers": ["Star-Lord", "Rocket", "Groot", "Drax"],
        "correct_answer": "Star-Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a green-skinned assassin in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "answers": ["Gamora", "Nebula", "Mantis", "Yondu"],
        "correct_answer": "Gamora"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a blue-skinned warrior in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "answers": ["Nebula", "Gamora", "Mantis", "Yondu"],
        "correct_answer": "Nebula"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a telepathic empath in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "answers": ["Mantis", "Gamora", "Nebula", "Yondu"],
        "correct_answer": "Mantis"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the character who is a blue-skinned Ravager in Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "answers": ["Yondu", "Nebula", "Gamora", "Mantis"],
        "correct_answer": "Yondu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the song played during the ride in Guardians of the Galaxy: Cosmic Rewind?",
        "answers": ["Hooked on a Feeling", "Come and Get Your Love", "Mr. Blue Sky", "I Want You Back"],
        "correct_answer": "Hooked on a Feeling"
    }
]